Guide to the New Dimensions Media records M1577
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
New Dimensions Media records
1968-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
New Dimensions Media
M1577
636.4 Linear Feet (6600 audiovisual elements, 66 feet manuscripts)
570 linear feet of media (circa 6600 quarter-inch audio tapes, DATs, cassettes, minidiscs, and CDs) and 66 linear feet of archival records, including organizational files, resource files, press/promotional and mailings, photographs and slides, NEW DIMENSIONS JOURNAL and NEWSLETTER, and business records. The tapes hold approximately 7000 hours of audio and video recordings.
Biographical / Historical
New Dimensions Media is an independent, listener supported, educational broadcasting group based in Ukiah, California. Interviews by the group are carried by public and community radio stations and feature a gamut of eclectic voices including artists, scientists, ecologists, social architects, healers, spiritual leaders, indigenous voices, etc. The program is broadcast in more than 500 communities nationally.
Conditions Governing Access
The print portion of accession 2008-144 is open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use. Audiovisual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy. The remainder of the collection is closed until processed.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gifts and purchases from New Dimensions Media.
New Dimensions Media
- Series 1: Accession 2008-144
  General
  See website for information about downloadable programs: https://newdimensions.org/
  - Sub-Series 1: Biographical information of interviewees
    Includes articles, promotional materials about books published, workshops, clippings and other.
    Biographical files for names with letter A through Mizzi; no files available for other names.
    - Abbey, Edward, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Program number
      2115
    - Abdullah, Sharif, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
      2794, 2991
    - Abo-Shaeer, Muhsin, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Abrams, Jeremiah, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      2265
    - Abukhalil, As'ad, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Unspecified
    - Aburdene, Patricia, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      3109
    - Achterberg, Jeanne, 1986-1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ackerman, Diane, 1991-2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Adair, Margo, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
      2915
    - "Patch" Adams Hunter, 1988-2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Adrienne, Carol, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
      2734
    - Aftel, Mandy, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Agor, Weston, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      1955, 2020
    - Aitken Roshi, Robert, 1980-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Alexander, Christopher, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Alexander, Shoshana, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Alexander, Theresa Sheppard, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      2642
    - Alexander, William M., 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Ali, A. Hameed (aka A. H. Almaas), 1990-2006 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      3168
    - Ali Akbar Khan, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Allegretti, Jan, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
      3025
    - Allen, Marc, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      3177
    - Allen, Paula Gunn, 1990-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      2202
    - Allen, Robert, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Allen, Steve, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
    - Allenbaugh, Eric (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Allione, Tsultrim, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      3253
    - Allende, Isabel, 1993-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
      2384, 2522, 2996
    - Alli, Antero, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Alt, Jeff, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      3149
    - Altemus, Barbara, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Progam number
      3128
    - Alter, Joel, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      2687
    - Amos, Wally (Famous Wally Amos), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Amritanandamayi ("Ammachi"), 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Amodeo, John and Kris Amodeo, 1985-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Anand, Margot, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Anderson, Nancy, 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Patricia, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Anderson, Richard feather, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Anderson, Walter Truett, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Anderson, William, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Andreas, Connirae, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      2464
    - Andreotti, Lindsay and Brian Hilgendorf, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      3182
    - Andrews, Lynn V., 1987-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2-4)
      Spirit of the Times
      Spirit of the Times is an unnumbered program series.
      1643, 1859, 1961, 2014, 2065, 2360, 2679
    - Andrews, Valerie, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Angelou, Maya, 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      1983
    - Angermeir, Carole, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Ansary, Tamin, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      2945
    - Anthony, Carl, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      2300
    - Apollon, Susan, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      3133
    - Arguelles, Jose, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      2317
    - Ariiyante, Dr. A.T., 2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Arjuna Ardagh, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      3093, 3103, 3218
    - Arkin, Alan, 1979-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Arms, Suzanne, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Armstrong, Anne and Jim Armstrong, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      2791
    - Armstrong, David and Elizabeth Metger Armstrong, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      2321
    - Aron, Elaine, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Arpaia, Joseph, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Arrien, Angels, 1980-2005 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
      2897, 3116 and unspecified
    - Artress, Lauren, 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Arvigo, Rosita, 1994-1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      2465
    - Atkinson, Kim (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Atlee, Tom and Jay Earley, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      2756
    - Auerbach, Stevanne, 1978-1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Augustine, Dennis, 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Auh-ho-oh, Choqosh, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Austen, Hallie Iglehart and Karen Vogel, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Austin, James, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      3044
    - Ausubel, Kenny, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      2818
    - Autry, James, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      2613, 2714
    - Avital, Samuel, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Babbitt, Bruce, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Bach, Richard and Leslie Parrish-Bach, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
    - Bache, Christopher and Winston Franklin, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      2866
    - Badiner, Allanin, 1990-2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      2197
    - Baez, Joan, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bagby, Rachel, 1994-1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      2454
    - Bailey, Betty, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Bailie, Gil (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Baker, Jeannine Parvati, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Baker, Mel, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Baker-Roshi, Richard (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Baldwin, Christina, 1994-1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Balin, Peter, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Ball, Carolyn M., 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Ballard, Carroll and Christina Ballard, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Ballard, James, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Ballentine, Rudoloh, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Banker, Deborah, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Banner, Bob, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Bantock, Nick, 1991-2001 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Banyacya, Thomas, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Baran, Joshua, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Barasch, Marc Ian, 1993-2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      2835, 2844, 3089
    - Baraz, Jim, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Barbach, Lonnie, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Barbour, Ian, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Barbour, Laurie-Ann, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Barigian, Warren, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Barlow, Connie, 1998-2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      3132 and unspecified
    - Barston, David, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Barzakoff, Ivan, 1978-1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Batchelor, Stephen, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Barrett, Richard, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Bateson, Mary Catherine, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Bawa (Guru), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Beacham, Frank, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Beagle, Peter S., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Beak, Sera, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1`6)
      3174
    - Bear, Ken Hawk, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Beattie Melody, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      2950
    - Becker Marys, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Beckwith, Micahel, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Beeman, David, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Beeman, David, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Beinfel, Harriet and Efrem Korngold, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      2291
    - Belitsos, Byron, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Bellah, Robert, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Belyea, Charles and Steven Tainer, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Bellamy, D. Richard, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Bender, Sue, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Benjamin, Medea and Kevin Danaher, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      3037
    - Bennett, Hal, 1987-1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Berardi, Alexander, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Berenholtz, Jim, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Berenholtz, Jim, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Berg, Peter, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
      2724, 2742
    - Berg, A. Scott, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Berman, Michael S., 2006 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      3148
    - Berman, Phillip, 1987-1997 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
    - Bernbaum, Edwin, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      2215
    - Berner, Charles, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Bernie, Barbara, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Berry, Ray, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Berry, Thomas, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      2611
    - Berry, Wendell, 1985-1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      2362
    - Bertani, Elizabeth (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Besher, Alexander, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bess, Donovan, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Bethards, Betty (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Bettelheim, Bruno, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Beymer, Sondra, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Bhaerman, Steve, 1992-2006 (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
      Proram number
      2346, 2659, 2994, 3146
    - Bhagavan Das, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Bhagavati, Ma Jaya, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Bielecki, Tessa, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Binder, Tim, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Bird, Christopher, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Bishop, James, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Program numbers
    - Black Elk, Wallaces, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Bioneers, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      S939, S940
    - Blackstone, Dick, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Blades, Lynn, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Blair, Lawrence and Lorne Blair, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Bloch, Douglas and Demetra George, 1987-2000 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Block, Bill, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Bloom. Allan, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Bloom, Linda and Charlie Bloom, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      3050
    - Bloomfield, Harold and Robert Cooper, 1995-2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      2523, 2824
    - Bluestein, Lawrence and Sanchez, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Blum, Ralph, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bly, Robert, 1985-1998 (Box 14, Folder 3-5)
      1678, 1854, 1966, 2140, 2052, 2244, 2568 and unspecified
    - Bogart, Greg, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Boggs, Grace Lee, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Bogue, Nila, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Bohm, David, 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      2071, 2072 2181, 2182
    - Boldt, Laurence, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bolen, Jean Shinoda, 1984-2006 (Box 15, Folder 4-6)
      1842, 1860, 1861, 2347, 2588, 2591, 2803, 2852, 3008, 3101, 3395
    - Bonheim, Jalaja, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      2644
    - Bonny, Helen, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Booker, Maruga, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Boorstein, Sylvia, 1997-2007 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      2671, 3205
    - Borg, Marcus J., 2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Borghum, Dale, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Borker, Cora (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Bortz, Wlater, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Borysenko, Joan, 1993-2007 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
      2190, 2387, 2627, 3072, 3214
      Spiriti of the Times
    - Bosnak, Robert, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      2579
    - Boulet, Susan Seddon, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bowles, Beatrice, 1989-1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Boxer, Barbara, 1999-2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Boyd, Andrew, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Boyd, Doug, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      2520 and unspecified
    - Boyle, Francis, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Braden Gregg, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      3186
    - Bradfield, Steve, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      2988
    - Bradford, Terry, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Bradley, Bills, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Bradley, Karyn, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Bradley, Marion Zimmer, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Bradshaw, John, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      2280
    - Brand, Stewart, 1972-1993 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Branden, Nathaniel, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      2441, 2559
    - Braun, Harry, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Braungart, Michael, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Brave Bird, Mary, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Breema (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Breathnach, Sarah Ban, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Brener, Anne, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      2453
    - Brenes, Abelardo, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Brennan, Barbara, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      2428
    - Breton, Denise and Christopher Largent, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Brewer, Spencer, 1990-1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Brezsny, Rob, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      3125
    - Bridges, William, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Briggs, Dennie, 1990-1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Brill, Steve Wildman, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Brill, Hal and Cliff Fegenbaum, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Briskin, Alan, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      2748
    - Brizendine, Louann, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      3179
    - Brodsky, Greg (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Brock, Gwen Jarrell (Box 19, Folder 2)
      1954
    - Broersma, Patricia, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      3233
    - Brook, Peter (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Brooks, Markell, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Broomfield, John, 1988-1998 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      2707
    - Brower David, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      2732
    - Brower, Kenneth, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Brower, Lincoln, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Anita (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Brown, Fred, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      3007
    - Brown, Juanita, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      3006, 3106, 3032 and one unspecified
    - Brown, Jerry, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      2258
    - Brown, Les, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Browne, Tom Jr., 1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Browne, Mary T., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Browne, Merry, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Brunsman, Elmer, 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Broyles, William Jr., 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bruchac, Joseph, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Brussat, Fred & Mary Ann, 1996-2000 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
      2604
    - Brutoco Rinaldo, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bruyere, Rosalyns, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      2552
    - Bryant, Barry, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bryson, David M. D., 2006 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Buchmann, Christina and Marcia Falk (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Buckley, Mary, 1984-1996 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Budapest, Z., 1989 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Daishin, Buksbazen, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Bullis, Juanita, 1993-1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Burke, Colleen, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Burnham, Sophy, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Burns, Khephra and Susan Taylor, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      2630
    - Burnum, Burnum, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Burr, Chuck, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      3251
    - Burstyn, Ellen, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Burton, Valorie, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Spirit of the Times is an unnumbered program series
    - Buscaglia, Leo, 1971-1988 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Butler, Katy, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Butterfield Englsh, Jane, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Buzan, Tony, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Byrne, Katy, 1992-1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Byrne, Rhonda, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Caddy, Peter and Paula Caddy, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Cahill, Sedonia, 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
      2686
    - Caldes, Marlene Fern, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Caldicott, Helen, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      2329
    - Callanan, Tom, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Callaway, Marguerite, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      3193
    - Callenbach, Ernest, 1993-1999 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Cameron, Julia and Mark Bryan and Tim Wheater, 1996-2003 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      2602, 2773
    - Campbell, Bebe Moore, 1986-2006 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Debold, Elizabeth, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Campbell, Don, 1994-2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      2506
    - Campfell, Joseph, 1975-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      1296, 1374, 1586, 1901
    - Campbell, Peter and Ed McMahon, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Campbell, Susan, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cane, Bill, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Capacchione, Lucia, 1989-2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Caple, John, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Cappadonna, Dominie, 1984-1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Capra, Fritjof, 1981-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
      2263, 2685 and unspecified
    - Caputi, Jane, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Carazo, Rodrigo, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Carey, Ken, 1988-1994 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      2449 and unspecified
    - Carlebach, Schlomo, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Carlino, Jill and Lewis Carlino, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Carlson, Clayton, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Carlson, Clayton, 1984-1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Carslon, Richard, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Carol, Bonnie, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Carpenter, Andre, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Carr, Kathleen Thormond, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Carroll, Paula, 1981-1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Carse, James, 1994-1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      2496, 2711
    - Carson, David, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Carter, Forrest, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 2000-2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      2856
    - Carter Scott, Cherie, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      2860
    - Casanova, Nicole, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cash, Paul, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Cashman, Kevin, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Cassim, Mohamed, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Castaneda, Carlos, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Casteel, Sean, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Castle, Christopher (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Catalfo, Phil, 1985-1998 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      2618
    - Chadwick, David, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Chagdud Tulku Rinpoche, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Chakravarti, Sree, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      2417
    - Chalanda Ma, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      2937
    - Chang, Iris, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Chan, Luke, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Chang, Richard, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Chappell, Tom, 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Master Charles, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Chaudhuri, Haridas, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Chavis, Meolody Ermachild, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      2665
    - Chetananananda, Swami, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Chia, Mantak and Maneewan Chia, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Chiche, Sophie and Mark Samuel, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Chickering, Sherman, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Chidananda, Brother, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      3076
    - Childers, Charlotte and Harriett Childers, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Chinen, Allan B., 1991 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Chimnoy, Sri, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Chitrabhanu, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Chodron, Thubten, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Choegyal, Richen Khandro, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Chopich, Erika and Margaret Paul, 1989-1995 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Chopra, Deepak, 1989-2004 (Box 27, Folder 1-4)
      2201, 2285, 2531, 2606, 2808
    - Chopra, Gautama, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Chow, Effie Poy Yew, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Christ, Carol P., 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      2688
    - Christian, Diana Leafe, 2003-2006 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      3010, 3273
    - Christopher Kay, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Church, Dawson, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      3213
    - Claassen, William, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Spirit o ftheTimes is an unnumbered program series.
    - Cleary, Thomas, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Cleese, John, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Clements, Alan, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
      2955
    - Clinton, Bill, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Clinton, Hilary, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Clow, Barbara Hand, 1992-2007 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      3218
    - Cochran, Tracy, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      2550
    - Coehlo, Paul, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Cody, Anna, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Cogburn, Elizabeth, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Cohen, Allan, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Cohen, Andrew, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
      3212
    - Cohen, Ben, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Michael, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Cole-Whittaker, Terry, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Coleman, Cathy, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Collaborative Law, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Collins, D. Jean, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Colorado, Apela, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Colorado, Pam, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      2224
    - Combs, Allen, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      3216
    - Combs, Deidre, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
      3051, 3111
    - Conforti, Michael, 1997-2005 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Connelly, Diane, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Conrad Da'oud, Emily, 1987-1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Conrad, Laurie (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Cooper, Rabbi David A., 1997 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Cooper, Jay, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      2788
    - Cooper, Robert, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Cooperrider, Allen, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Cooperrider, David, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Coppola, Francis Ford, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Cornell, Judith, 1990-2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      Spirit of the Times is an unnumbered series.
    - Cosgrove, Tracy, 1990-1996 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Cosmic Lady, 1989-1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Cotler, Lanny, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Council for a Parliamanent of the World's Religions, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Cousens, Gabriel, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
      3056
    - Cousineau, Phil, 1991-2004 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Cousines, Norman, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Cousteau, Jacques, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cousteau, Jean Michel (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Cown, Elio, 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Cowell, Adrian, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Cowles, Kristi, 1990-1999 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Cox, Harvey, 2003-2005 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      3081
    - Coyote, Peter, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Craft, Caroly, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Craighead, Meinrad, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      2262
    - Crandall, B. C., 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Creme, Benjamin, 1981-1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Crichton, Michael, 1979-1988 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Crimmins, Jack, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Crockett, Paul and Sylvie Crockett, 1980-1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Croswell, Ken, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Crowe, Thomas, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      3143
    - Crum, Tom, 1987-1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Csikszentmihalyi, Mihaly, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      2578
    - Cumes, Dave M.D., 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Cusumano, Joseph D., 1997-2001 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      2660
    - Cuttillo, Brian, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Cuttin, Janet, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Da Freejohn, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Da Vid, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Daddio, Michael, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Dail, Hilda Lee, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 5)